# Seisuke Yamada

seisuke.ym@gmail.com (236) 688-3422 Burnaby, BC seisuke.info linkedin.com/in/seisuke atthub.com/seihello

Front-end developer with a Bachelor's degree in Computer Science and 5+ years of experience in software development. Also have taken the lead on several projects and have overseen a team of about 10 developers. Currently working as a Next.js developer and have implemented 15+ features to web application. I consistently engage in coding activities and learning new technology on a daily basis while working on a group project. Considered responsible and detail-oriented, I contribute to team goals with a passion for building efficient, maintainable, and user-friendly systems.

## Work Experience

## Full Stack Web Developer Internship (Remote)

Aug. 2023 - Present

Summations, Toronto, ON

- Develop a web application for generating a clipped image of citation using Next.js.
- Implemented 15+ interactive features and refactored the code for easy maintenance.
- Collaborated with another developer to refine designs and achieve user-friendly application.

## Full Stack Web Developer Internship

Jun. 2023 - Aug. 2023

Sandman Media Inc., Vancouver, BC

- Built corporate websites and achieved optimal design and layout across different devices and screen sizes.
- Completed a sophisticated animation as a client desired, leaving the client satisfied.
- Created a reusable CMS component, allowing non-programmers to easily customize content and format, accordingly enhancing development efficiency. The component was applied to 5+ websites as a result.
- Developed a feature to automatically fetch articles from an RSS feed and add them to the database, making the process of updating articles efficient.

## Software Engineer / Project Manager

Apr. 2017 - Aug. 2022

Murata Machinery, Kyoto, Japan

- Architected and built a large-scale C++ application for controlling thousands of machines operating in semiconductor manufacturing facilities. Developed 50+ complex features within 5 years.
- Communicated with clients and users to propose improvements and created required specifications.
- Designed UI in compliance with product specifications, resulting in reduced operational errors and improved visibility of progress status.
- Created test specifications to inspect the application with utilizing techniques such as decision table.
- Supervised 10+ programmers and designers, assigned tasks, and reviewed deliverables.
- Led a team for boosting the development speed. Restructured the development process by dividing the steps and set new procedures for testing and reviewing. Consequently, the timeline reduced by 3 months.

## Education

Diploma: Web Development

Jan. 2023 - Present

Cornerstone International Community College of Canada, Vancouver, BC

Bachelor: Computer Science and Engineering

Kyoto Sangyo University, Kyoto, Japan

Apr. 2017 - Aug. 2022



Computer Language: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, C, C++, Python, Java, Dart

Framework: JQuery, React, Next.js, Node.js, Flutter, Selenium

Database: MySQL, PostgreSQL, Apache Cassandra Git, Firebase, Joomla!, Jenkins, Figma

Methodology: DevOps, Agile Development

Soft Skill: Problem solving, Time management, Attention to detail, Leadership, Teamwork

### **Q** Honors & Awards

Murata Machinery Special Recognition
3rd place in the university coding contest
JASSO Scholarship
Jun. 2021
Dec. 2014
Mar. 2013

### □ Projects

### **Transportation Controller**

C, C++, Vue.js, WebSocket, Google Test, UML, Git, SVN, Jenkins

A large-scale application that controls thousands of machines transporting products in semiconductor factories. It finds optimal transport routes, efficiently dispatches tasks, and manages transportation status. Comprised of numerous processes, it operates across multiple computers while communicating each other. Its screen displays a map of the factory, the machine status, errors, and other relevant information. It also allows the users to send commands to the machines.

#### 

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Next.js

A single-page web application that displays information related to article or paper citations. Users can resize the card, choose its design, add a QR code or customize other things before exporting the information as an image.

#### 

HTML, CSS, Sass, JavaScript, PHP, Joomla!

A multi-page corporate website designed for responsiveness. It includes features such as news feeds, a sign up function, and a stock price display, all of which are driven by custom CMS components. An automation script fetches RSS feeds and updates the news page by adding content to the database.

#### 

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.js, Express, EJS

A multi-page web application for shortening long URL. Users can add as many URLs as they like, and they can refer back to them even after leaving the page. It has user registration and login features, and manages cookies to control the login state.